ROBERT SMITH

Sr. Sap Security Administrator

Phone: (0123)-456-789 | Email: info@qwikresume.com | Website: Qwikresume.com

SUMMARY

8+ years of experience working in IT industry. 5+ years of experience working in SAP security Administration & Authorizations. Almost 3 years of professional experience working in Ruby on Rails framework. Having very good implementation knowledge of OOP's concepts. Experience in front end development using jQuery, Coffeescript, Ajax etc.

CORE COMPETENCIES

SAP 4.6 & 6.0, MS Office 2003-2016, Mainframe, MS Outlook And Lync, AS/400 Server, Wireless, LAN/WAN.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sr. Sap Security Administrator

ABC Corporation - July 2007 - November 2020

Key Deliverables:

- Worked on the implementation of new module SAP xRPM.
- Involved in designing and developing abap/portal roles for xRPM.
- Worked in designing roles and creating users at mass level for ESS.
- Interacted with supplier/service provider ensure tasks are completed.
- Verified back up, daily check list, account maintenance.
- Administered tape rotation back up tapes.
- Served as the point of technical escalation.

Sap Security Administrator

Delta Corporation - 2006 - 2007

Key Deliverables:

- Duration 02/2010 06/2011 Environment SAP ECC 6.0, SAP CRM 7.0, SAP R/3 4.6/4.7, CLARITY, EARS Remedy Tool, Cisco VPN Client, MS Office, Windows XP/.
- Duration 03/2009 01/2010 Environment SAP ECC 6.0, SAP R/3 4.6/4.7, CLARITY, Profile Generator (PFCG), EARS Remedy Tool, Cisco VPN Client, MS Office,.
- Installation of the ECC 6.0, R/3 4.6 and 4.7 Apply patches using SPAM for BASIS, ABAP, and HR modules Configured Transport Management System for ECC.
- Configuration of R/3 for remote connection with SAP Browsing Service Market Place for latest Updates in SAP and applying latest Support Packs & DSS.
- Environment SAP ECC 6.0, SAP R/3 4.6/4.7, CLARITY, Profile Generator (PFCG), EARS Remedy Tool, Cisco VPN Client, MS Office, Windows XP/2000.
- Created Portal roles and have the Portal development team map iViews to the appropriate portal roles.
- Add roles to the User Groups which is created in Active Directory Implemented and worked with SSO (Single Sign-On) on all the systems in landscape.

ROBERT SMITH

Sr. Sap Security Administrator

Phone: (0123)-456-789 | Email: info@qwikresume.com | Website: Qwikresume.com

EDUCATION

B-Tech - (JNT University - Hyderabad, Andhra Pradesh)